<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CUPA Adoption</string>
    <string name="tab_aa">Active Adoptions</string>
    <string name="tab_pa">Passive Adoptions</string>
    <string name="tab_fc">Foster Care</string>
    <string name="tab_sa">Successful Adoptions</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sa">Successful Adoptions</string>
    <string name="aa">Active Adoption</string>
    <string name="pa">Passive Adoptions</string>

    <string name="whatfc">What is Foster Care?</string>
    <string name="whatfcex">
        Some animals, especially young ones need a safe and\n
        nurturing environment to grow and recover.\n
        They require direct individual attention that no\n
        shelter can provide.\n\n

        This is where YOU can step in to make a difference.\n\n

        Foster parents help CUPA by taking home one of our\n
        shelter animals, either a dog or cat, and taking\n
        full care of it until a permanent home is found.\n
        This includes covering the basic needs and costs\n
        associated with keeping a pet, such as food and\n
        everyday medication if required. If the foster pet\n
        is need of a major surgery or expensive medication,\n
        it can be done in consultation with CUPA.\n\n

        The pet will require the complete attention of the\n
        Foster parent and the time it needs to be ready for\n
        adoption. Fostering a pet is an extremely rewarding\n
        experience, as it will socialise the pet to a home\n
        environment and possibly get it used to being around\n
        other pets and people too. All of this other than\n
        the fact that, you will get to cuddle with your\n
        foster child and enjoy his or her company without\n
            a permanent commitment!\n
    </string>

    <string name="canifc">Can I provide Foster Care?</string>
    <string name="canifcex">
        You can certainly provide Foster Care to an animal\n
        when you are:-\n\n
        1. Able to give your complete attention to\n
           recovering or young animal.\n
        2. If you are fostering a dog, take him or her for\n
           regular walks.\n
        3. Make regular visits to the clinic and monitor\n
           her recovery and growth.\n
        4. Able to cover bulk costs of food, basic\n
           medication, maintenance expenses.\n
           (CUPA can pitch in too!)\n
        5. Ensure that the pet is vaccinated and sterilised\n
           before giving it up for adoption.\n
        6. Able to free up the space required to\n
           accommodate the animal in your home.\n
        7. When all members of the family are vaccinated\n
           against rabies and are open to having\n
           a pet at home.\n
        8. It would be ideal if former pet owners take up\n
           a Foster animal, as extra sensitivity towards\n
           animals is required for successful and\n
           smooth fostering.\n
    </string>

    <string name="howlongfc">How long do I need to Foster?</string>
    <string name="howlongfcex">
        It is ideally recommended that the animal be in\n
        Foster Care till a permanent and loving home is found.\n
        This is because too many transfers can be confusing\n
        and difficult for a young one. The animal can either\n
        be adopted or taken back to the shelter if a space\n
        opens up, both of which could take anywhere from\n
        2 weeks to 2 months. It is also very likely that our\n
        shelter will be full – we receive over 20 calls a day\n
        for the rescue of injured or abandoned animals.\n\n

        As for adoption the Foster Parent will have to look for\n
        a suitable family for their ward, through social media,\n
        newspaper advertisements, etc. They would also have to\n
        screen families who are interested in adopting their ward,\n
        in order to make sure the animal is put into a loving\n
        and safe home.\n\n

        The permanent adopter will have to present an ID proof\n
        and address proof. Also, to term the adoption as\n
        “successful” a representative will make a home visit\n
        2 to 4 weeks after the adoption, to check if the animal\n
        is doing well and is comfortable in its new home.\n
    </string>
</resources>
